=Love For Two Lives=
= الحب لعمرين =
=Episode 18=
= الحلقة 18 =
Mom.
أم.
My son!
ابني!
You've been in bed for almost a year.
لقد كنت في السرير لمدة عام تقريبًا.
Now you're finally awake.
الآن أنت مستيقظ أخيرًا.
She really brought good luck.
لقد جلبت حقا حظا سعيدا.
My son is awake.
ابني مستيقظ.
It's all superstition.
إنها كلها خرافات.
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
That's what Mr. Longlang said.
هذا ما قاله السيد Longlang.
Your son got better
تحسن ابنك
because the medicine I gave him worked.
لأن الدواء الذي أعطيته له نجح.
Why are you coughing?
لماذا تسعل؟
I've spent so many years finding treatment to no avail.
لقد أمضيت سنوات عديدة في العثور على العلاج دون جدوى.
Do you think I'll believe what you said?
هل تعتقد أنني سأصدق ما قلته؟
You fed him so much wrong medicine.
لقد أطعمته الكثير من الأدوية الخاطئة.
It only made him worse.
هذا فقط جعله أسوأ.
You were fooled.
لقد تم خداعك.
Stop it!
توقف عن ذلك!
What's wrong with your throat?
ما خطبك في حلقك؟
What do you mean by that?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
Are you saying I'm stupid?
هل تقول انني غبي؟
Fine. Kill her.
بخير.  أقتلها.
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
You can kill her if you want.
يمكنك قتلها إذا أردت.
But if you do,
ولكن إذا فعلت ذلك ،
I won't treat your son.
لن أعالج ابنك.
Think about it.
فكر في الأمر.
It's a hopeless case anyway.
إنها حالة ميؤوس منها على أي حال.
Why don't you let me try?
لماذا لا تدعني أحاول؟
What if I can make him better?
ماذا لو استطعت أن أجعله أفضل؟
Right?
حق؟
I think that makes sense.
اعتقد ان هذا منطقي.
Okay.
تمام.
I'll let you live for a few more days then.
سأدعك تعيش لبضعة أيام أخرى بعد ذلك.
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
Guard the door.
حراسة الباب.
Kill whoever comes out.
اقتل من يخرج.
Let's go.
لنذهب.
This is not a place to stay long.
هذا ليس مكانا للبقاء طويلا.
Let's not get into fights with these bandits.
دعونا لا ندخل في معارك مع قطاع الطرق هؤلاء.
We should leave at night.
يجب أن نغادر في الليل.
I can't go, Your Majesty.
لا أستطيع الذهاب يا جلالة الملك.
The Young Master
السيد الشاب
got better now,
تحسنت الآن ،
but he might go back to the earlier state
لكنه قد يعود إلى الحالة السابقة
if I don't continue the treatment.
إذا لم أستمر في العلاج.
I've promised them anyway.
لقد وعدتهم على أي حال.
I can't go back on my words.
لا أستطيع التراجع عن كلماتي.
Are you sure you can treat him?
هل أنت متأكد أنك تستطيع علاجه؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
My grandpa is a doctor.
جدي طبيب.
His illness is very common in my hometown.
مرضه شائع جدا في مسقط رأسي.
I only need a few days.
أنا فقط بحاجة لأيام قليلة.
Okay.
تمام.
Do it then.
افعلها بعد ذلك.
We'll stay here together.
سنبقى هنا معا.
I'm so disappointed.
انا محبط.
This is a great opportunity.
هذا هو فرصة عظيمة.
How can you help them?
كيف يمكنك مساعدتهم؟
Do you want to be the Queen or nor?
هل تريد أن تكون الملكة أم لا؟
Aunt.
عمة.
It's all my fault.
هذا كله خطأي.
But I don't want to fight for the title
لكني لا أريد أن أقاتل من أجل اللقب
with these despicable tricks anymore.
مع هذه الحيل الحقيرة بعد الآن.
Despicable?
حقير، خسيس؟
I've lived my whole life in this palace.
لقد عشت حياتي كلها في هذا القصر.
The biggest lesson I learned
أكبر درس تعلمته
is that you can't afford to be weak-minded.
هو أنك لا تستطيع أن تكون ضعيف الذهن.
Aunt.
عمة.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
I don't want to see you today.
لا اريد ان اراك اليوم.
Leave.
غادر.
Yes.
نعم.
What's this?
ما هذا؟
♪Traces of time and space, and forgotten galaxies♪
آثار الزمان والمكان ، والمجرات المنسية
♪Time alternates our relationship♪
الوقت يتناوب علاقتنا ♪
♪The sea of stars is pretty and quiet♪
♪ بحر النجوم جميل وهادئ
♪The rain touches the breath♪
المطر يمس النفس ♪
♪Get close to you♪
♪ اقترب منك